In this video, I'm going to show you how
I use AI to create the sales copy that
has generated multiple eight figures for
my clients, myself, and how you can do
the same to have an eight figure level
copywriting skill that you don't need to
have been trained in copywriting, but
you can utilize the right AI prompting
to be able to do this. And so, I'm going
to show you kind of my thought process
behind it. Number one, I got to tell
you, most people are using AI the wrong
way. And you want to make sure that you
can learn how to communicate it. By the
end of this video, you're going to know
how to communicate with the artificial
intelligence to know exactly what to
say, how to say it, and how to get the
results that you want. And if you watch
all the way to the end, I promise you,
you're going to have your marketing
figured out what you want to do, and
what you want to get done this year,
what you got to do in the next six
months, what you got to do in the next
30 days. You're going to have that all
mapped out for you very simply, very
easily. So, let's dive right into it. If
you don't have a chat GPT account, I'm
going to tell you this. Maybe you're
like, "I've used AI before. It's not as
good as I want it to be." Can I tell you
this? It's gotten a lot better in the
last couple of months, and it's only
getting better. Artificial intelligence
has it it it improves almost double. I
want I want you to remember this. It
gets like twice as good
every 3 to six months. And that's a
crazy thing because like there's nothing
else on the planet right now that is
like that that gets twice as good.
You're not going to have twice as better
of a toothbrush or a car or a stove,
right? But artificial intelligence gets
twice as good about every 6 months. Even
computers or cell phones don't improve
that much. But AI right now, it's a
different type of growth curve in AI
because of all of the money that's being
spent into it. So understand, maybe you
used it six months ago, maybe you used
it a year ago and you're like, "Oh man,
it was crappy." Can I tell you
something? It's not anymore. And so I've
gotten to the place where I was like six
months, even a year ago, I was like, we
don't use AI that much as much for stuff
because I don't want it to sound bad.
Now I'm like, okay, the AI really is a
big part of what we're doing because it
works and it gets the results. So you
got to have a chat GPT account. And I
highly recommend you have a chat GPT
plus account because it's going to give
you access to the 03 algorithm. 03
is the best algorithm that you can use
for a lot of different stuff. When we do
copyrightiting, I often use 40. What's
the difference between 03 and 40? It's
so confusing. And this right here is why
people don't utilize AI. They're
confused by the fact that there's two
algorithms. There's so many of them
different ones out there. And so they
would rather struggle than learn maybe
how to use them. That's not you.
Luckily, unfortunately, maybe 30 to 50%
of the people watching this video
clicked off and they go went and watched
a Kardashian video instead because they
got overwhelmed by the fact that there's
two algorithms. But not you. You're
watching this and I'm going to show you
how to use it the right way. So, when
we're writing sales copy, I go between
these two. I use 03 a lot of times to
brainstorm and come up with research and
then I use 40 for the final writing. And
so, that's what we're going to do right
here. We're going to start with 03. And
let's just say that you are a coach that
helps parents be able to reach and and
work with their kids and and it helps
parents to not be so overwhelmed each
day. Okay. So, I want to say I help
parents not be so overwhelmed
each day in their life and
I have a coaching program around this to
bring the family together.
Brainstorm for me.
And and and here's the cool thing about
this. I actually have a chat GPT prompt
document over at my website. And this is
where it gets really kind of fun. over
at jeremiahowski.com.
Go to jeremiah kowski.com.
This is me right here. And free AI
prompts is right in the top corner here.
Wh my little my little camera screen is
kind of in the way of you seeing that.
Let me move my let me move my camera to
the bottom corner here. Free AI prompts.
They're right here. Okay.
And this will give you my prompt
document with some of my best prompts.
And I'm constantly updating and
iterating these types of things. So, we
have right here a master marketing
prompt right here. This one comes up
with ideas for you that you can use to
come up with different coaching
programs, things like that. How you
might uh utilize those types of things.
So, let's just say I'm going to put that
in here. I'm going to say, "Brainstorm
for me a complete $997 coaching program
in the specified niche. Include detailed
descriptions of the core components."
And so, the AI is going to go to work
and it's going to start thinking. This
is the new thing about what 03 does.
It's a thinking algorithm. it it starts
to process and think and come up with
ideas and then it gives you the output.
So here's a program snapshot, family
flow formula, weekly live coaching
implementation sessions. Okay, what
we're doing right now is we're not
necessarily going to utilize all of
this, but we're setting the foundation
for it to write better sales copy for
us. Excuse me.
Take a drink of water here. By the way,
this is raw and real and that's how I
make a lot of my videos. I don't you
don't need to do a bunch of editing and
a bunch of stuff like that with them. Um
it's just not even worth your time. And
so I want I just want to encourage you
like if you're out there making content,
you don't need to be perfect with it.
You can be raw and real as you're making
content. Okay, so that's given us a
bunch of great ideas. Social media
content, YouTube videos, even email
marketing, all that. Okay. Now, what
we're going to do is we're going to have
it build out.
Let me see. Act as an expert in online
sales and marketing. Refine the offer to
make it a lot better and more persuasive
for Facebook ads. So, specifically
around what is marketable on social
media and Facebook ads. And I think that
that's going to be a big part about it
because
oftent times
when we go to market something on social
media, it's not as compelling to the
social media audience. And so what this
does is this is going to overhaul it to
be something that's more positioned for
social media. The calm catalyst system.
Overcome quantified hours in 8 weeks.
There we go. Okay. And this has come up
with like a lot of different ideas that
you can offer and things like that.
How overwhelmed are your days? 90 90
second parent burnout quiz. That's
pretty cool.
Uh live webinar story bridge from pain
to mechanism to proof offer stack
10-minute calm routine. So this is kind
of giving us a lot of our our marketing
ideas
and what we're going to create something
around. Again, this is just feeding it
into the machine to help us refine what
this is. Now, I'm going to use this
prompt to help me come up with my sales
copy for my landing page. Anytime you're
creating an offer,
you want to utilize a landing page. I
have an offer right here all about
Instagram ads. This is sales copy for my
Instagram ads offer that people can
download. I have an evergreen marketing
class right here that people can
download and check out. This is sales
copy right here. So everything that we
start with starts with that sales copy.
So I always utilize this prompt as if
I'm creating a webinar. Webinars and
challenges are still the best way to get
clients. We like to automate them and
put them on demand. And even when I'm
creating a video like this, I still
treat it as if it's the concept of a
webinar. I come up with my ideas for my
YouTube videos with the ideas of a
webinar. So let's say this is a free
webinar from meltdowns to mellow. How to
slash household chaos by 80% in weeks.
Are you sick of mornings that feel like
a liveaction disaster movie? I've been
there, too. Searching for missing shoes.
Okay, this is great. Watch this.
So, this created this. Make me a
photograph to go with my sales page to
match this sales copy. I'm going to copy
that sales copy that it created. And the
AI is actually going to go to work and
create a photo that matches the scene
that will go on here. Oftentimes when
we're creating sales letters, we put
photos that match the scene that we're
talking about.
Okay.
Here's here's some more right here.
There's a photo. I'll use photos of me
oftent times. Um, there's a new offer
that I'm I'm creating though right here
where if I can pull this one up, you'll
see kind of how I
do this.
I want to show you this right here. This
one's a brand new offer. It's not out
there to the public yet, so we're still
tweaking it. This is an image of
somebody who's struggling to post daily
and get all that stuff going. Okay. So,
what we're doing is we're generating an
image of the scene that matches what it
is that you are promoting.
It's going to take a takes a little bit
to generate these images, but it's a
great tool that can allow you to really
go in with your messaging. Then, what I
do is I'm going to copy this prompt as
well, and we want to really dive deeper
into what are the pain points, what are
the problems, and all of that to process
it.
and go through this for our sales copy.
This will be our next prompt that we're
going to give it after it creates this
image for us. All right. So, there's the
graphic. It took quite a while to
create. That's why I had to pause the
video here, but you could use an image
like that to for your page right there.
So, what I do now is I go through and I
go and grab the other prompts that are
on here. And the reason why is again we
want to feed this information into the
machine. When we can feed the
information into the machine, it greatly
allows us to be able to come up with
ideas for our sales copy that work so
much better for our offer. So, I'm going
to feed this one in here now. It's going
to give us answers to the pain points
and the objections and the things that
keep our prospect up at night and and
help us dial this in even deeper.
Let the thinking algorithm go through
to do this. And this is the process that
I use for every single offer sales copy.
I I personally utilize these exact same
prompts
every single day, every single week for
my clients that I work with. So, it's
worth doing. Okay. So, it's going to
generate for us some pain points, waking
up behind on schedule, common
objections, what keeps them up at night,
top frustrations,
mindset issues, uh, you know, here's
some headlines that you could utilize,
problem, agitate, solution, ADA, copy.
Okay.
Now, one thing that you could do if you
want to speed this up, you could just
paste all of these different prompts in
here, um, except for the last one
because I want to save that one. And
with 03, it'll sequentially go through
each step and actually generate all of
them, which is really cool. You weren't
able to do that before, but that can
also speed you up. You could literally
go through and grab steps number one
through five
and just paste all that in there as
well. and it will it will each one go
through and start to generate. Okay,
here's our backstory. Here's our we used
to have to do this all manually. Now
it'll with 03, it'll literally do it in
one prompt, which is super super cool to
be able to go through and dial that in.
Um, and that just shows you the power of
how much better these AI algorithms have
gotten at what they can accomplish. We
have the the results generator right
here, the outcome generator. This is
what I love. We dive deeper into the
outcome. Okay. So, now I'm going to take
all that. We're going to go to prompt
number six. And this is where the sales
copy gets really, really good for our
offer that we're going to put out there.
It's going to do it as a storytelling
sales copy that's going to identify the
issue and the problem and it's going to
have empathy attached to it is a big
part about it. Okay. Are you tired of
mornings that feel like a live action
disaster movie? The alarm blarers,
babies cry, somebody lost a shoe. And in
fact, I would actually do this one. This
is I made a mistake here. I would redo
this one with the 40 instead of 03.
We'll use 40 because it's going to be a
lot better at writing the way that we
want it to write. Are you tired of
feeling like your house runs you instead
of the other way around? That's great.
Are you tired? Are you sick of mornings
that feel like a disaster movie? You
know the scene. One kid's screaming
about socks. The other's crying about
cereal. Being the wrong shape. Your eggs
are
I've been there. It almost broke me. I
remember. After tripping over a
backpack, nearly spilling my coffee.
This does sound like my morning
sometimes. Now mornings feel calm.
Breakfast is made and eaten. Shoes are
found. In our evenings they end in
laughter, not bribes or breakdowns. From
meltdowns to mellow. How to slash
household chaos by 80% in eight weeks.
And so that could be for your coaching
program right there if we wanted to
create that.
And and this is just one example of how
we utilize AI to help us put together
great sales copy. In my wealthy coach
academy program, I work with you to help
you develop your offers, your sales
message to know exactly what it takes to
be able to dial this all in and get the
results that we want. I'm excited. I I I
look forward to working with you. If you
are a coach, mentor, trainer, and you
want to get more results in your
business and you want to dial things in,
I'm here with you to help you to be able
to do that. Jump in, check out the info
about my Wealthy Coach Academy program.
I'd love to see you in there and we'll
talk soon. Make sure to subscribe to
this channel for more videos like